Okay, so this will be a very short video in this video. I'm going to tell you just one thing. Okay, so as you can see that
We had one locked user component here like sorry locked user variable here, which we have declared
So make sure to take this destructure it out of the author store and this locked user will be
Will be in this condition like locked user and and and then we are going to just display all of these
Okay, so that's it and another thing is that like let me show you
When we go to the front and write so this whatever this example email is and
Let me pass this one
So logging in successful right. So as you can see this profile picture here
This profile picture we have to like we are still to create that
Update profile pic light, right. So in that case
We don't have the option to in the front and side. We don't have the option to upload the image from our side
So we can either one thing you can do you can go to the postman and just
Like upload your image like I've soon earlier, right?
You can take some sample image from the Google and you can include that in your back end and then you can try to access that
That login page, but by now. We don't have by for now. We don't have this profile pic, right?
so that is one thing and
One more update is here that like if you go to this
Author controller.js makes you to earth controller.js. We have
Wait a second once again
In this line, please make sure to pass the complete user data instead of just a three rows. Okay, so
Whatever three data just to move that and pass complete user information here. So that is one update. Okay
So make sure to do these changes and I will see you in the next video